Long John Nebel Papers
Long John Nebel Papers
- Tapes
  - LJN All Night Show
    - "Louise" Edited From James Lee Interview, April 29, 1969; nebel_1649; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 82)
    - "Student Riots" (repeated 1969 May 13) Al Lottman, Kenneth Knigin, David Schulte, Edward Winter, April 30, 1969; nebel_1650-1652; 3 reels (Oversize 82)
    - "The Pill" (repeated 1969 June 29) Dr. Sherwin Kaufman, Dr. Hanna Kapit, May 3, 1969; nebel_1653-1655; 3 reels (Oversize 83)
    - "Phones" (5-6AM) Kenneth Knigin, May 3, 1969; nebel_1656-1657; 2 reels (Oversize 83)
    - "Expedition to Find Lost City Of Incas" (repeated 1969 June 22) James Rand, Roger Caras, Frederik Pohl, May 7, 1969; nebel_1658-1660; 3 reels (Oversize 83)
    - (repeated 1969 September 23) Zorita, Edward Spingarn, Paris Flammonde, May 8, 1969; nebel_1661-1663; 3 reels (Oversize 83)
    - Zorita, May 8, 1969; nebel_1664; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 83)
    - "Phones" (4-6 AM) Ken Knigin, May 10, 1969; nebel_1665-1666; 2 reels (Oversize 83)
    - "New Prostate Operation" Dr. Robert L. Rowan, May 15, 1969; nebel_1667; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 83)
    - "Phones" (4-6 AM) Long John Nebel, May 17, 1969; nebel_1668-1669; 2 reels (Oversize 83)
    - "Cancer Research" (repeated 1969 October 5) Dr. Donald Cole, Sanford Teller, May 21, 1969; nebel_1670-1672; 3 reels (Oversize 83)
    - (repeated 1969 May 29) Robert Carson, Al Lottman, May 23, 1969; nebel_1673-1675; 3 reels (Oversize 84)
    - "Phones" (4-6 AM) Long John Nebel, May 24, 1969; nebel_1676-1677; 2 reels (Oversize 84)
    - (repeated 1969 May 28) Dr. Hanna Kapit, Robert Cochnar, May 27, 1969; nebel_1678-1680; 3 reels (Oversize 84)
    - "Phones" (3-5 AM) Sanford Teller, May 30, 1969; nebel_1681-1682; 2 reels (Oversize 84)
    - "Phones" (3-6 AM) Or. Robert Davis, May 31, 1969; nebel_1683-1685; 3 reels (Oversize 84)
    - "Phones" (4-6 AM) Long John Nebel, June 7, 1969; nebel_1686-1687; 2 reels (Oversize 84)
    - "Aliens In The Skies" (repeated 1969 June 17; 1969 August 31) John G. Fuller, Frederik Pohl, Sanford Teller, June 13, 1969; nebel_1688-1690; 3 reels (Oversize 84)
    - "Phones" (4-6 AM) Long John Nebel, June 14, 1969; nebel_1691-1692; 2 reels (Oversize 84, 85)
    - "Phones" (2:30-5 AM) Alan Cornet, June 18, 1969; nebel_1693-1694; 2 reels (Oversize 85)
    - "Spencer Tracy" (repeated 1969 June 24) Larry Swindell, Sanford Teller, Robert Carson, Paul Domitrovich, June 19, 1969; nebel_1695-1697; 3 reels (Oversize 85)
    - "Phones" (3-5 AM) Long John Nebel, June 19, 1969; nebel_1698-1699; 2 reels (Oversize 85)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, June 21, 1969; nebel_1700-1702; 3 reels (Oversize 85)
    - "The Birth Of God" (repeated 1969 September 14) James Kavanaugh, Paris Flammonde, Kenneth Knigin, June 25, 1969; nebel_1703-1705; 3 reels (Oversize 85)
    - "Judy Garland Autopsy" Cyril H. Wecht, June 28, 1969; nebel_1706; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 85)
    - "Golf Cart Races" Ernie Myers, July 4, 1969; nebel_1707; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 85)
    - Dr. Cyril Wecht, Dr. S. Fineberg, Alan Cornet, July 12, 1969; nebel_1708-1713; 6 reels (Oversize 85, 86)
    - "Phones" Kenneth Knigin, July 19, 1969; nebel_1714-1715; 2 reels (Oversize 86)
    - "Phones" Kenneth Knigin, July 21, 1969; nebel_1716-1718; 3 reels (Oversize 86)
    - "Phones" Sanford Teller, July 22, 1969; nebel_1719-1723; 5 reels (Oversize 86)
    - "Question Of Autopsy In Ted Kennedy Case" Dr. Cyril Wecht, July 24, 1969; nebel_1724; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 86)
    - "Phones" Sanford Teller, July 26, 1969; nebel_1725-1726; 2 reels (Oversize 86)
    - "Phones" (3-5) (repeated 1969 August 7) Sanford Teller, Phil Foster, Ed Winter, July 29, 1969; nebel_1727-1729; 3 reels (Oversize 86)
    - "Phones" (12-2:30) Sanford Teller, August 5, 1969; nebel_1730-1732; 3 reels (Oversize 86, 87)
    - "Phones" (2-4 AM) Ken Knigin, August 9, 1969; nebel_1733-1734; 2 reels (Oversize 87)
    - "Phones" (12-2:30 AM) Ken Knigin, August 10, 1969; nebel_1735-1736; 2 reels (Oversize 87)
    - "Phones" (Stock Market) Robert Carson, August 14, 1969; nebel_1737-1738; 2 reels (Oversize 87)
    - "The Emerging Republican Majority" (repeated 1969 December 14) Kevin P. Phillips, Seena Hamilton, Al Lottman, August 16, 1969; nebel_1739-1741; 3 reels (Oversize 87)
    - "Phones" (3-4 AM) Al Lottman, August 16, 1969; nebel_1742; 1 reel (Oversize 87)
    - "Phones" (12-3 AM) Al Lottman, August 17, 1969; nebel_1743-1745; 3 reels (Oversize 87)
    - "Phones" (12-2:30) Ken Knigin, August 19, 1969; nebel_1746-1748; 3 reels (Oversize 87)
    - "Phones" (3-4 AM) Long John Nebel, August 23, 1969; nebel_1749; 1 reel (Oversize 87)
    - "Phones" Ken Knigin, August 24, 1969; nebel_1750-1751; 2 reels (Oversize 87)
    - "Phones" (12-2:30) Bentley Kassal, Don Maclean, August 26, 1969; nebel_1752-1754; 3 reels (Oversize 87, 88)
    - "Phones" (12-4 AM) Sanford Teller, August 30, 1969; nebel_1755-1758; 4 reels (Oversize 88)
    - "Phones" (12-2:30) Edward Winter, August 31, 1969; nebel_1759-1761; 3 reels (Oversize 88)
    - "Phones" (12-2 AM) Ken Knigin, September 2, 1969; nebel_1762-1763; 2 reels (Oversize 88)
    - (repeated 1969 December 7) Dr. Hyman Chartock, Paris Flammonde, Edith Aynes, September 5, 1969; nebel_1764-1766; 3 reels (Oversize 88)
    - "Phones" (12-3 AM) Sanford Teller, September 7, 1969; nebel_1767-1769; 3 reels (Oversize 88)
    - (repeated 1969 September 18) Rev. Arthur Ford, Kenneth Knigin, September 9, 1969; nebel_1770-1771; 2 reels (Oversize 88)
    - (repeated 1969 September 17; 1969 September 27) Mel Torme, Lester Del Rey, Frederik Pohl, September 13, 1969; nebel_1772-1773; 2 reels (Oversize 88)
    - "Phones" (12-3 AM) Sanford Teller, September 23, 1969; nebel_1774-1776; 3 reels (Oversize 89)
    - "Phones" (12-3 AM) Sanford Teller, September 28, 1969; nebel_1777-1779; 3 reels (Oversize 89)
    - "Behavior Control" (repeated 1969 October 1; 1969 November 30) Dr. Perry London, Allen Cornet, Frederik Pohl, September 30, 1969; nebel_1780-1782; 3 reels (Oversize 89)
    - "Phones" Sanford Teller, October 5, 1969; nebel_1783-1785; 3 reels (Oversize 89)
    - "Phones" (3-4 AM) Long John Nebel, October 9, 1969; nebel_1786; 1 reel (Oversize 89)
    - "Phones" (3-4 AM) Ken Knigin, October 11, 1969; nebel_1787; 1 reel (Oversize 89)
    - "Phones" (12-3 AM) Sanford Teller ** MISSING after 1995 storm, October 12, 1969; nebel_1788-1790; 3 reels (Oversize 89)
    - "Vietnam Moratorium" Kieran O'Doherty, Al Lottman, October 15, 1969; nebel_1791-1793; 3 reels (Oversize 89)
    - "Phones" (4-4:30 AM) Alan Cornet, October 16, 1969; nebel_1794; 1 reel (Oversize 90)
    - (repeated 1969 October 23) Al Stevens, Al Lottman, Sanford Teller, October 18, 1969; nebel_1795-1797; 3 reels (Oversize 90)
    - "Phones" (2:30-3:30 AM) Sanford Teller, October 18, 1969; nebel_1798; 1 reel (Oversize 90)
    - "Phones" (12-3 AM) Seena Hamilton, Al Lottman, October 22, 1969; nebel_1799-1801; 3 reels (Oversize 90)
    - "Phones" (3-4 AM) Ken Knigin, October 25, 1969; nebel_1802; 1 reel (Oversize 90)
    - Gary Barker, Sanford Teller, Gene Sanger, October 31, 1969; nebel_1803-1805; 3 reels (Oversize 90)
    - George Lincoln Rockwell, Martin Berger, Rev. Robert Schrock, Charles Raddick, undated; nebel_1806-1810; 5 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 90)
    - "Behind The Dim Unknown" Rev. John Clover Monsma, undated; nebel_1811-1812; 2 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 90)
  - LJN Early Hour
    - "Long John Nebel vs. Marguerite Haymes on Unitology", January 29, 1968; nebel_1047; 1 reel (Oversize 52)
    - "Long John Nebel vs. Bill Kuhns" (repeated 1968 March 14), January 30, 1968; nebel_1053; 1 reel (Oversize 53)
    - "Zionism" Rabbi Aaron Pearl, John Gutermann, January 31, 1968; nebel_1058; 1 reel (Oversize 53)
    - "Long John Nebel vs. Dr. Howard B. Miller, A Dentist Who Claims To Have Found A Cancer Cure", February 1, 1968; nebel_1059; 1 reel (Oversize 53)
    - "My Friend The Dictator" Cindy Adams, February 6, 1968; nebel_1067; 1 reel (Oversize 53)
    - Daniel H. Watts, Rev. Arthur Bradford, February 7, 1968; nebel_1078; 1 reel (Oversize 54)
    - Larry Ellman, February 8, 1968; nebel_1079; 1 reel (Oversize 54)
    - Joseph Kottler, David A. Schulte, February 9, 1968; nebel_1081; 1 reel (Oversize 54)
    - "Fluoridation" Dominick Paduano, February 12, 1968; nebel_1089; 1 reel (Oversize 54)
    - "Long John Nebel vs. Pauline Peavy, Trance Medium", February 14, 1968; nebel_1091; 1 reel (Oversize 54)
    - Gray Barker, February 15, 1968; nebel_1100; 1 reel (Oversize 55)
    - "Supreme Court Rulings" (repeated 1968 March 22) Commissioner Lowell B. Mason, Al Lottman, February 16, 1968; nebel_1102; 1 reel (Oversize 55)
    - (repeated 1968 May 27) Jack Shepherd, February 19, 1968; nebel_1105; 1 reel (Oversize 55)
    - "Vietnam" Rev. Richard Neuhaus, David Schulte, February 20, 1968; nebel_1106; 1 reel (Oversize 55)
    - "Marriage" Dr. Erika Freemin, Straight Line, February 21, 1968; nebel_1111; 1 reel (Oversize 55)
    - Woodrow Derenberger, February 21, 1968; nebel_1112; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 55)
    - "Credit Cards" (repeated 1968 April 10) Jules Asch, February 22, 1968; nebel_1116; 1 reel (Oversize 56)
    - Ron Carey, February 28, 1968; nebel_1131; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 56)
    - Dr. A. Jarrette, David Schulte, March 1, 1968; nebel_1136; 1 reel (Oversize 57)
    - "Bulls, Bears And Dr. Freud" (repeated 1968 April 29) Albert Haas, Joel Fisch, March 5, 1968; nebel_1140; 1 reel (Oversize 57)
    - (repeated 1968 April 2) Dr. Oliver York, March 6, 1968; nebel_1144; 1 reel (Oversize 57)
    - (repeated 1968 April 1) Jack Sherby, March 8, 1968; nebel_1151; 1 reel (Oversize 57)
    - "Meatless Cooking" (repeated 1968 April 12) Pegeen Fitzgerald, Terry Garrity, March 19, 1968; nebel_1160; 1 reel (Oversize 58)
    - (repeated 1968 June 27) Leon Henry Jr., Terry Garrity, March 21, 1968; nebel_1164; 1 reel (Oversize 58)
    - "American Telephone Consumers Council" George Levine, Sanford Teller, March 22, 1968; nebel_1165; 1 reel (Oversize 58)
    - Dr. Allan M. Wolfe, March 29, 1968; nebel_1172; 1 reel (Oversize 58)
    - Rabbi Hollander, Dan Watts, phones on Martin Luther King assassination after news reported tragedy, April 4, 1968; nebel_1173; 1 reel (Oversize 58)
    - "Psychic Stories" Sanford Teller, April 5, 1968; nebel_1176; 1 reel (Oversize 59)
    - "The A.D.A." (repeated 1968 July 1) Bentley Kassal, David Schulte, April 17, 1968; nebel_1184; 1 reel (Oversize 59)
    - Irwin Greif, April 18, 1968; nebel_1194; 1 reel (Oversize 60)
    - "Operation Match" Steve Milgrim, April 24, 1968; nebel_1198; 1 reel (Oversize 60)
    - "Possibility Thinking" Rev. Robert Schuller, April 25, 1968; nebel_1202; 1 reel (Oversize 60)
    - Gary MacEoin, Sanford Teller, May 1, 1968; nebel_1214; 1 reel (Oversize 61)
    - "Consumer Frauds" Moe Greenspan, May 2, 1968; nebel_1215; 1 reel (Oversize 61)
    - "Flying Saucer Fiasco" John G. Fuller, May 3, 1968; nebel_1219; 1 reel (Oversize 61)
    - "Columbia University Riots" Rabbi Aaron Pearl, Al Lottman, May 9, 1968; nebel_1224; 1 reel (Oversize 61)
    - "Starting And Succeeding In Your Own Small Business" (repeated 1968 July 8) Louis L. Allen, Daniel Watts, May 15, 1968; nebel_1225; 1 reel (Oversize 61)
    - "Social Psychology" Dr. Richard I. Evans, May 17, 1968; nebel_1226; 1 reel (Oversize 61)
    - Emory Lewis, Sanford Teller, May 22, 1968; nebel_1227; 1 reel (Oversize 61)
    - Dorothy Uhnak, Al Lottman, May 22, 1968; nebel_1228; 1 reel (Oversize 61)
    - "School Battle" Roger Caras, Marilyn Braverman, Richard Rowson, May 22, 1968; nebel_1232; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 61)
    - Valerie Moolman, Terry Garrity, May 23, 1968; nebel_1233; 1 reel (Oversize 61)
    - (repeated 1969 March 18) Brian Daly, May 31, 1968; nebel_1246; 1 reel (Oversize 62)
    - "Robert Kennedy Assassination" Dr. Hanna Kapit, Dr. Howard Millet, Dr. Theodore I. Rubin, Dr. Cyril H. Wecht, June 5, 1968; nebel_1251; 1 reel (Oversize 62)
    - "Robert Kennedy Assassination" Dr. Theodore Rubin, Dr. Cyril Wecht, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Dr. Howard Miller [MISSING tape 1253], June 5, 1968; nebel_1252-1253; 2 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 62)
    - "The Town That Went Mad" John G. Fuller, June 11, 1968; nebel_1261; 1 reel (Oversize 63)
    - Dr. Jack R. Ferber, Dr. Howard B. Miller, June 13, 1968; nebel_1265; 1 reel (Oversize 63)
    - "What's In A Word?" Dr. Mario Pei, Dr. Edward Spingarn, June 14, 1968; nebel_1266; 1 reel (Oversize 63)
    - "Diary Of A Witch" (repeated 1969 November l) Dame Sybil Leek, Seena Hamilton, June 18, 1968; nebel_1270; 1 reel (Oversize 63)
    - "To The Year 21000" (repeated 1968 August 6) Criswell, June 20, 1968; nebel_1271; 1 reel (Oversize 63)
    - E. Donald Shapiro, Sanford Teller, June 25, 1968; nebel_1276; 1 reel (Oversize 64)
    - Dr. Theodore I. Rubin, June 26, 1968; nebel_1281; 1 reel (Oversize 64)
    - "Sex: Female, Religion: Catholic" Sally Cunneen, Robert Cochner, July 2, 1968; nebel_1282; 1 reel (Oversize 64)
    - Rt. Rev. Arnold M. Lewis, Robert Schrook, July 3, 1968; nebel_1283; 1 reel (Oversize 64)
    - Robert Theobald, Al Lottman, July 10, 1968; nebel_1291; 4 reels (Oversize 64)
    - "Large Metropolitan Hospital" Alan Cornet, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, July 11, 1968; nebel_1296; 1 reel (Oversize 65)
    - "Plastic Surgery" (repeated 1968 August 30; 1968 December 11) Dr. Joseph S. Consentino, July 11, 1968; nebel_1297; 1 reel (Oversize 65)
    - Dr. Geoffrey Lindenauer, Dr. Emerson Coyle, July 17, 1968; nebel_1302; 1 reel (Oversize 65)
    - "Merchants of Heroin" Alvin Moscow, Arthur Grennan, July 19, 1968; nebel_1303; 1 reel (Oversize 65)
    - Willie J. Smith, Daniel H. Watts, July 25, 1968; nebel_1308; 1 reel (Oversize 65)
    - "What Can Modern Hypnotism Do For You?" Sidney Petrie, July 26, 1968; nebel_1309; 1 reel (Oversize 65)
    - "Welfare" Leah Marks, Seena Hamilton, July 30, 1968; nebel_1314; 1 reel (Oversize 66)
    - "Police In Court" Abraham Gerges, Norman Frank, July 31, 1968; nebel_1319; 1 reel (Oversize 66)
    - "Great Eating For Weight Watchers" Dr. Carleton Fredericks, August 1, 1968; nebel_1324; 1 reel (Oversize 66)
    - "Gun Control" Steve Elias, Abner Cohen, August 2, 1968; nebel_1325; 1 reel (Oversize 66)
    - "The Jacques Romano Story" Dr. Berthold Schwartz, August 9, 1968; nebel_1330; 1 reel (Oversize 66)
    - "Frozen Death" Saul Kent, August 13, 1968; nebel_1334; 1 reel (Oversize 67)
    - "New Definition Of Death And Transplants" Harry H. Lipsig, Bob Cochnar, August 14, 1968; nebel_1339; 1 reel (Oversize 67)
    - Dr. Frederick Franck, Gary MacEoin, August 15, 1968; nebel_1344; 1 reel (Oversize 67)
    - "Psychiatry" Dr. Charles W. Socarides, 1968 August 22-23; nebel_1353; 1 reel (Oversize 68)
  - LJN Phone Show
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, Candy Jones, Rex Harrison, January 3, 1967; nebel_0597-0598; 2 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 30)
    - "Night Mayor and Book Review" Long John Nebel (Phones), January 17, 1967; nebel_0613; 1 reel (1/4"x600') (Oversize 31)
    - "Phones", March 13, 1967; nebel_0675; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 34)
    - Al Lottman, Morton Shulman, March 15, 1967; nebel_0676-0677; 2 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 34)
    - "Anyone Can Make A Million" (aired 1967 September 26) Dr. Morton Shulman, Al Lottman, Robert Metz, March 15, 1967; nebel_0678-0680; 3 reels (Oversize 34)
    - Sanford Teller, Donald MacLean, March 22, 1967; nebel_0688-0690; 3 reels (2 copies No. 1 reel) (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 35)
    - Phone Show, April 24, 1967; nebel_0717; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 36)
    - "Phones" Dr. Richard Ireland, May 23, 1967; nebel_0741; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 37)
    - Bill Mazer "Phones" (Long John Nebel), June 13, 1967; nebel_0766; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 39)
    - "Girl From Venus" Vivenus, June 23, 1967; nebel_0773; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 39)
    - "Mammography" Dr. S. K. Fineberg, June 23, 1967; nebel_0774; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 39)
    - "Catholic Church" Fr. James Kavanaugh, August 6, 1967; nebel_0807; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 41)
    - "Phones", September 11, 1967; nebel_0853; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 43)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, September 12, 1967; nebel_0855; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 43)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, September 18, 1967; nebel_0862-0863; 2 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 43)
    - "Phones", October 4, 1967; nebel_0882; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 44)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, October 5, 1967; nebel_0883; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 44)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, October 12, 1967; nebel_0887; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 45)
    - "Why The Taxi Strike?" Edward Winter, November 14, 1967; nebel_0914; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 46)
    - "Phones" Sanford Teller, December 13, 1967; nebel_0952; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 48)
    - "Poverty" Robert Cochnar, December 14, 1967; nebel_0956; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 48)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, December 20, 1967; nebel_0966; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 48)
    - Earl Wilson Jr., December 22, 1967; nebel_0973; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 49)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 4, 1968; nebel_0992; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 50)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 5, 1968; nebel_0994; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 50)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 8, 1968; nebel_1002; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 50)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 9, 1968; nebel_1004; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 50)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 10, 1968; nebel_1008; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 50)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 12, 1968; nebel_1010; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 50)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 15, 1968; nebel_1017; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 51)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 16, 1968; nebel_1019; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 51)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 17, 1968; nebel_1024; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 51)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 18, 1968; nebel_1029; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 51)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 19, 1968; nebel_1033; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 52)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 22, 1968; nebel_1039; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 52)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 23, 1968; nebel_1041; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 52)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 24, 1968; nebel_1043; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 52)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, January 25, 1968; nebel_1044; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 52)
    - Richard Clarke, January 30, 1968; nebel_1054; 1 reel (1/4"x600') (Oversize 53)
  - LJN Versus
    - "Sterilization" H. Curtis Wood Jr., December 12, 1966; nebel_0581; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 30)
    - "Motherhood" (repeated 1968 August 8) Seena Hamilton, June 27, 1967; nebel_0779-0780; 1 reel (Oversize 39)
    - "Long John Nebel vs. Milbourne Christopher on Magic", September 11, 1967; nebel_0854; 1 reel (Oversize 43)
    - "The Young Divorcees" (repeated 1968 July 29) Lissa Charell, November 1, 1967; nebel_0898; 1 reel (Oversize 45)
    - Dr. S. K. Fineberg, Dr. Ben C. Scharf, November 28, 1967; nebel_0926; 1 reel (Oversize 46)
    - "Frozen Death" Saul Kent, January 4, 1968; nebel_0991; 1 reel (Oversize 50)
    - (repeated 1968 March 18) Rev. George Kandle, January 5, 1968; nebel_0993; 1 reel (Oversize 50)
    - Rabbi Aaron Pearl, January 8, 1968; nebel_1001; 1 reel (Oversize 50)
    - Bentley Kassal, David A. Schulte, January 9, 1968; nebel_1003; 1 reel (Oversize 50)
    - "Women" Seena Hamilton, January 10, 1968; nebel_1005; 1 reel (Oversize 50)
    - "Air Pollution" Gary Leeder, January 11, 1968; nebel_1009; 1 reel (Oversize 50)
    - (repeated 1968 April 8) David A. Schulte, Bentley Kassal, January 15, 1968; nebel_1016; 1 reel (Oversize 51)
    - (repeated 1968 March 25; 1968 August 29) Dr. Robert Rowan, January 16, 1968; nebel_1018; 1 reel (Oversize 51)
    - Rex Reed, Sanford Teller, January 17, 1968; nebel_1020; 1 reel (Oversize 51)
    - "Transplants" (repeated 1968 March 13) Fred Pohl, Rev. Robert Schrock, January 18, 1968; nebel_1025; 1 reel (Oversize 51)
    - "Sex And Your Heart" (repeated 1968 February 2; 1968 March 15) Myron Brenton, January 22, 1968; nebel_1038; 1 reel (Oversize 52)
    - "Diet Pills Scandal" (repeated 1968 February 3; 1968 June 10) Dr. S. K. Fineberg, January 23, 1968; nebel_1040; 1 reel (Oversize 52)
    - "Black Power" (repeated 1968 January 31) John O. Killens, January 24, 1968; nebel_1042; 1 reel (Oversize 52)
  - Monitor
    - Gladys Philpot, January 13, 1966; nebel_0364; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 19)
    - "Hospital Crisis" Edwin Hoyt, December 10, 1966; nebel_0580; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 30)
    - "Hypnosis" Dr. Leo Wollman, December 19, 1966; nebel_0589; 1 reel (Oversize 30)
    - "Spoiled Priest" Gabriel Longo, January 7, 1967; nebel_0602-0603; 2 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 31)
    - "A Search For The Truth" Ruth Montgomery, March 12, 1967; nebel_0674; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 34)
  - Straight Line
    - Wayne Howell, February 1, 1968; nebel_1060; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 53)
    - Ralph Kaufman, February 2, 1968; nebel_1064; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 53)
    - Robert Low, February 3, 1968; nebel_1065; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 53)
    - Roger Caras, February 5, 1968; nebel_1066; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 53)
    - Jean Pierre Hallet, February 6, 1968; nebel_1071; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 53)
    - John Marion, February 6, 1968; nebel_1072; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 53)
    - "The Naked Ape" Desmond Morris, February 6, 1968; nebel_1073; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 53)
    - James Kavanaugh, February 8, 1968; nebel_1080; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 54)
    - "Air Pollution" Robert A. Fox, February 10, 1968; nebel_1088; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 54)
    - Alan Cornet, February 13, 1968; nebel_1090; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 54)
    - Rabbi David Hollander, February 14, 1968; nebel_1096; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 55)
    - Dr. Robert Cushing, February 15, 1968; nebel_1101; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 55)
    - Emerson Coyle, February 16, 1968; nebel_1103; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 55)
    - Lester Del Rey, February 17, 1968; nebel_1104; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 55)
    - Eli Belil, February 20, 1968; nebel_1110; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 55)
    - Leonard Sloane, February 22, 1968; nebel_1117; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 56)
    - "Microwave Cooking" Clifford H. Lane, February 27, 1968; nebel_1127; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 56)
    - "Tone-A-Matic Belt" Donald J. Wineman, May 1, 1968; nebel_1213; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 61)
    - "Meatless Cooking" Pegeen Fitzgerald, May 3, 1968; nebel_1220; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 61)
    - Stephen Huffaker, June 6, 1968; nebel_1257; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 63)
  - WOR
    - "LJN'S Stories", August 24, 1962; nebel_0001-0003; 3 reels, 7" (Oversize 1)
  - Unknown shows
    - "Christmas Show", December 22, 1965; nebel_0350-0351; 2 reels (1/4"x1200'), 7" (Oversize 18)
    - "The Odds Against Me" (repeated 1967 April 5) John Scarne, Jack London, Roy Schatt, Kenneth Knigin, March 26, 1966; nebel_0395-0398; 4 reels (Oversize 20)
    - "The Gypsies" Jan Yoors, Sanford Teller, Sam Vandervirt, January 22, 1967; nebel_0619-0620; 2 reels (Oversize 31, 32)
    - Sterling Yates, Al Lottman, Danny Crystal, March 26, 1967; nebel_0695-0697; 3 reels (Oversize 35)
    - "Gorilla Show" Fred Weintraub, Charles Ryan, Sterling Yates, Danny Crystal, April 12, 1967; nebel_0700-0702; 3 reels (Oversize 35, 36, 39)
  - Miscellaneous
    - "Fair Play For Cuba Committee" Lee Harvey Oswald, circa 1962; nebel_1814; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 90)
    - "Murder Of Lee Harvey Oswald" Jack Ruby, 1966; nebel_0596; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 30)
    - "Kidney Transplant Appeal", March 15, 1969; nebel_1607; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 80)